<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Fath Pen</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Fath Pen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 20:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fathpen.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/getting-started/</guid><description>&lt;p>Geekblog is a simple Hugo theme for personal blogs. It is intentionally designed as a fast and lean theme and may not fit the requirements of complex projects. If a more feature-complete theme is required there are a lot of got alternatives out there. This post helps you to get started with the Geekblog theme, including initial setup and basic configuration.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Simple sticky posts</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/sticky/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 00:06:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/sticky/</guid><description>Sticky (or pinned) posts implementation is currently really simple and handled by weight: 1 in a post front matter.</description></item><item><title>Deployments</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/deployments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/deployments/</guid><description>Netlify Subdirectories Netlify There are several ways to deploy your site with this theme on Netlify. Regardless of which solution you choose, the main goal is to ensure that the prebuilt theme release tarball is used or to run the required commands to prepare the theme assets before running the Hugo build command.
Here are some possible solutions:
Use a Makefile:</description></item><item><title>Shortcodes</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/shortcodes/</guid><description>&lt;!-- markdownlint-disable MD024 -->
&lt;p>The theme bundles some handy shortcodes that tries to cover common situations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mermaid</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/mermaid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/mermaid/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a class="gblog-markdown__link" href="https://mermaidjs.github.io/">Mermaid&lt;/a> is library for generating SVG charts and diagrams from text.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ToC</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/toc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/toc/</guid><description>Simple wrapper to generate a page Table of Content from a shortcode.
{{&amp;lt; toc &amp;gt;}} Level 1 Level 2 Level 2.1 Level 2.1.1 Level 2.1.1.1 Level 2.1.1.1.1 Level 2.2 Level 1 Dolor sit, sumo unique argument um no. Gracie nominal id xiv. Romanesque acclimates investiture. Ornateness bland it ex enc, est yeti am bongo detract re.</description></item><item><title>Post with images</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/post-with-images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/post-with-images/</guid><description>If you need more flexibility for your embedded images, you could use the img shortcode. It is using Hugo&amp;rsquo;s page resources and supports lazy loading of your images.
Attributes:
Name Usage default name (string) Name of the image resource defined in your front matter. empty alt (string) Description for displayed image. resource .Title size (string) Thumbnail size (tiny|small|medium|large). empty lazy (bool) Enable or disable image lazy loading.</description></item><item><title>Markdown syntax</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/markdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/markdown/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Short post</title><link>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/post-short/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://fathpen.github.io/posts/post-short/</guid><description>Dolor sit, sumo unique argument um no. Gracie nominal id xiv. Romanesque acclimates investiture. Ornateness bland it ex enc, est yeti am bongo detract re. Pro ad prompts feud gait, quid exercise emeritus bis e. In pro quints consequent, denim fastidious copious quo ad. Stet probates in duo.</description></item></channel></rss>